(Sheldon:)but it works for Princeton, too.
(Amy:)Scavenger hunts at Harvard
were really tough.
(Amy:)I always got stuck
on the first challenge.
Trying to End someone
to be on a team with me.
(Amy:)I guess that story's
more sad than funny.
(Penny:)I love scavenger hunts. My friends
and I had them all the time.
(Leonard:)Oh, these are a little different.
(Leonard:)There's a tradition
at elite universities.
(Howard:)And Princeton.
(Leonard:)A tradition of hunts full of puzzles
that rely on logic,
(Leonard:)obscure knowledge, science.
(Penny:)Oh, in ours we would just run
around town looking for a store
(Penny:)that would sell us beer.
-So, who's in?
-I think it sounds fun.
(Amy:)-Yeah, me, too.
-I'm in.
(Various:)-Let's do it.
-I'm sorry.
(Sheldon:)Are we really doing this
or are we tricking Koothrappali again
(Sheldon:)like with the dinner party?
I (THEME SONG PLAYING) I